CORE SKILLS

- CAD Drafting (utilize AutoCad, Visio, Compass)
- Technical proficiency: stay updated on the latest CAD software tools
- Food Chemistry
- Engineering science
- Technology solutions
- Quality control
- Research and analysis
- Disciplined with high attention to
- Web: HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Webpack, Git

LANGUAGE

- English ESOL Entry Level 3
- Ukrainian fluent
- Russian fluent
- Slovak elementary

PERSONAL QUALITIES:

- punctual
- organized
- hardworking

INTERESTS

- playing the piano
- snowboarding
- playing checkers
- hiking in the mountains

CONTACT

Location: London

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/viktoriia-

sheveria

Telephone: +447385696993

Email: viktoriia.ianuta@gmail.com GitHub: https://github.com/ProstoVika

VIKTORIIA SHEVERIA

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a focused and ambitious developer. I am looking for an opportunity to demonstrate my strong work ethic, logical problems problem-solving and communication skills. I have some experience in chemical engineering, and private enterprise.

PROJECTS

More recently I have decided to further develop my skills and try my hand at programming, choosing to focus my studies on Front-end and the programming language — Java Script.

During this period I worked on many projects. I have included a small selection of them and if you wish to learn more visit my portfolio.

GitHub to see the rest:

https://github.com/ProstoVika

CAREER SUMMARY

2007 - 2013

Employer: Kyiv National University of Food Technologies Role: Laboratory technician, Kyiv

I worked as a laboratory assistant at the university in the chemical laboratory of scientific experiments in the food industry.

Main duties

- Perform laboratory tests in order to produce reliable and precise data;
- Ensure the laboratory is well-stocked and resourced;
- Following strict methodologies to carry out analyses;
- Prepare specimens and samples

2014 - 2015

Employer: Private enterprise Role: Accounting, Khust

I worked for a private enterprise as an economist and part-time logistician. In this job I had experience in teamwork, developing good working relationships with employees and making use of my clear communicative skills and ability to quickly my clear communicative find solutions or alternatives.

Main duties:

- Prepare financial statements and reports;
- Maintain accurate records of financial transactions.

2018 - 2019

Employer: Corporation "Ukrainian Mineral Waters" Role: Chemical engineer, Svaliava

I worked as a chemical engineer scientific freedom, having sole responsibility for deciding which raw materials could go through the technological processes to become a finished.

Main duties:

- analysis on raw materials, intermediates, and production batches throughout the manufacturing process in a timely manner;
- Maintaining organisation of data records, reference standards, procedures within the Quality department;
- Recognise trends within data records and producing reports regarding these trends.

EDUCATION HISTORY

2007-2013 **Kyiv National University of Food Technologies**Bachelor's degree in food technology engineering

2013-2014 **Odesa National Academy of Food Technologies** *Master's qualification in engineering*

2022-2023 FoxmindEd

Front-end Development (Angular). Completed an immersive sixmonth internship, gaining practical experience.